Guide to the Amsterdam News photograph archive, Series A. Subject Files K-O, 1920-2012.
Amsterdam News photograph archive
- Series A. Subject Files
  - Subject Files M
    - Macklin, Buford (Box A-77, Folder 71)
      Print has single-leaf press release from U.S. Department of Housing and Urban Development attached.
    - Macklin, James (Box A-77, Folder 72)
      Print is cut out and mounted on board.
    - MacLean, Malcolm S. (Dr.) (Box A-77, Folder 73)
    - Macombs Dam Bridge (Box A-77, Folder 74)
    - Macomson, William (Box A-77, Folder 75)
    - Macon, Thelma (Mrs.) (Box A-77, Folder 76)
    - Macon, Yvonne (Box A-77, Folder 77)
    - Macy, John, Jr. (Box A-77, Folder 78)
      Photographer if identified: Wagner International Photo Inc.
    - Macy's (Box A-77, Folder 79)
    - Madden, George (Mr. & Mrs.) (Box A-77, Folder 80)
    - Madden, Will (Box A-77, Folder 81)
      Photographer if identified: H. J. Fields
    - Maddox, Derrick (Box A-77, Folder 82)
    - Maddox, Elliott (Box A-77, Folder 83)
    - Maddox, Gweldolyn (Box A-77, Folder 84)
    - Maddox, Jacqueline (Box A-77, Folder 85)
      Print has single typescript leaf description attached.
    - Maddox, Lester (Governor) (Box A-77, Folder 86)
    - Maddox, Mary (Box A-77, Folder 87)
    - Maddox, Muriel (Box A-77, Folder 88)
      Also two negatives (two images total).
    - Maddox, Priscilla (Box A-77, Folder 89)
    - Madero, Rita (Box A-77, Folder 90)
      Also two velox prints. One print has photocopied newspaper clipping attached to verso with staples on border; two have typescript resumes (three leaves each) attached with staples on border; one has staples on border.
    - Madgeline, Mary (Box A-77, Folder 91)
      Photographer if identified: Clanton III
    - Madhubutti, Haki (Box A-77, Folder 92)
    - Madigan, Francis J. (Box A-77, Folder 93)
      Photographer if identified: N.Y.C. Housing Authority Photo Unit
    - Madison, Alfreda (Box A-77, Folder 94)
      Photographer if identified: James Gilbert, Jesse E. Woodley
    - Madison, Alma Smith (Box A-77, Folder 95)
      Print has been cut out.
    - Madison, Arthur A. (Box A-77, Folder 96)
      Print has single typescript leaf letter attached with paperclip.
    - Madison, Collin (Box A-77, Folder 97)
    - Madison, Frank (Bishop) (Box A-77, Folder 98)
      Print has single typescript leaf caption attached with staple on border.
    - Madison, Gloria (Box A-77, Folder 99)
      Photographer if identified: Jerry Sager
    - Madison, Mary (Box A-77, Folder 100)
    - Madison, Richard (Box A-77, Folder 101)
      Photographer if identified: Care Photo
    - Madison, Robert P. (Box A-77, Folder 102)
      Photographer if identified: Department of State Photographer
    - Madison, Rosie (Mrs.) (Box A-77, Folder 103)
    - Madison, Wanda (Box A-77, Folder 104)
    - Madison, William (Box A-77, Folder 105)
      Also one computer-printed leaf (image of a map of districts in Manhattan).
    - Madrid, Mae (Box A-77, Folder 106)
      Photographer if identified: Gaston Devigne
    - Madrid Restaurant (Box A-77, Folder 107)
      Also one typescript leaf letter.
    - Madry, George M. (Rev.) (Box A-77, Folder 108)
      Photographer if identified: A. Hansen, Harris Photo
    - Maduro, Morris (Box A-77, Folder 109)
    - Mae, Verta (Box A-77, Folder 110)
      One print is attached to folder; one has single-leaf press release attached on verso.
    - Mae, Willi & Mrs. (Box A-77, Folder 111)
    - Magalee, John (Rev.) (Box A-77, Folder 112)
    - Magby, Ruby (Box A-77, Folder 113)
      Also one negative (two images total). Two prints have single-leaf press releases attached with staples on border; one has staple in border; one has single letterpress printed business card attached with paperclip.
      Photographer if identified: Keno-Foto Service, Photokraft, Andrew J. Odom
    - Magee, Ruby (Ms.) (Box A-77, Folder 114)
    - Magee, Ruckell (Box A-77, Folder 115)
      Photographer if identified: United Press International Inc.
    - Magee, Sylvester (Box A-77, Folder 116)
    - Magic Touch (Box A-77, Folder 117)
    - Magill, Jerome (Box A-77, Folder 118)
    - Magill, John Thurston (Box A-77, Folder 119)
    - Magnatones, The (Box A-77, Folder 120)
    - Maginley, Edward (Mr. & Mrs.) (Box A-77, Folder 121)
      Photographer if identified: John Gardner
    - Maglie, Sal (Box A-77, Folder 122)
      Photographer if identified: News Release Photograph from Public Relations Department The F. & M. Schaefer Brewing Co.
    - Magliore, Paul (Box A-77, Folder 123)
      Photographer if identified: Hamilton Wright
    - Magliore, Aresne Eugene (Box A-77, Folder 124)
    - Maglorie, Paul (Box A-77, Folder 125)
      Two single-leaf press releases.
      Photographer if identified: James L. League, Office National Du Tourisme, James C. Campbell, Pan American World Airways, Dietz Photo
    - Magloire, Paul (Mrs.) (Box A-77, Folder 126)
    - Magnard, Valerie (Box A-77, Folder 127)
    - Magnetics, The (Box A-77, Folder 128)
    - Magnificent Monta-Gue (Box A-77, Folder 129)
    - Magnolia Tree, The (Box A-77, Folder 130)
    - Magubela, Yohance (Box A-77, Folder 131)
    - Maguire, John J. (Bishop) (Box A-77, Folder 132)
    - Maguishon, Eugene (Box A-77, Folder 133)
    - Mahaffey, Theodore (Box A-77, Folder 134)
    - Mahajan, Barbara (Box A-77, Folder 135)
    - Mahal, Taj (Box A-77, Folder 136)
      Also one velox. One print has typescript press release (five leaves attached with paperclip; one has typescript press release (three leaves) attached with paperclip, one has single-leaf press release attached with staple on border.
    - Mahamed, Meusi (Box A-77, Folder 137)
    - Mahammed, Ibrahim (Box A-77, Folder 138)
      Photographer if identified: U.S. Agency for International Development
    - Mahan, Beverly (Box A-77, Folder 139)
    - Maharat, Ralph (Box A-77, Folder 140)
    - Mahmoud, Murray A. (Box A-77, Folder 141)
    - Mahn, Linford L. (Box A-77, Folder 142)
    - "Mahogany" (Box A-77, Folder 143)
      30 prints have single typescript leaf descriptions attached. Many prints show Diana Ross.
    - "Mahogany" (Box A-77, Folder 144)
      15 prints have single typescript leaf descriptions attached. One print has typescript press release (14 leaves) attached with paperclip.
    - Mahone, Barbara (Box A-77, Folder 145)
    - Mahone, Juanita (Box A-77, Folder 146)
    - Mahoney, Glenn R. (Mrs.) (Box A-77, Folder 147)
      Photographer if identified: Kal Kern Photography
    - Mahoney, James T. (Box A-77, Folder 148)
    - Mahony, James (Box A-77, Folder 149)
    - Mahood, Joe (Mr. & Mrs.) (Box A-77, Folder 150)
      Photographer if identified: Dummett, Dave Greene Photo
    - Mahood, Joseph (Box A-77, Folder 151)
    - Mahood, Joseph & Lottye (Box A-77, Folder 152)
    - Maier, Henry W. (Box A-77, Folder 153)
    - Maillard, Lucille (Box A-77, Folder 154)
    - Main Ingredient, The (Group) (Box A-77, Folder 155)
      Also two velox prints. Three prints have single-leaf press releases from AM News attached.
    - Maine, Denise Du (Box A-77, Folder 156)
      Back of print reads: "Denise Du Maine."
    - "Mai Mars" (Box A-77, Folder 157)
    - Maingot, Marcella (Box A-77, Folder 158)
    - Mains, Dorothy (Box A-77, Folder 159)
    - Mainstream Dinner (Box A-77, Folder 160)
      Photographer if identified: Alvin J. Burley
    - Maiocco, Richard (Box A-77, Folder 161)
      Photographer if identified: Triboro Stadium
    - Mair, Lucille (Box A-77, Folder 162)
    - Mair, Richard (Box A-77, Folder 163)
    - Mais, Edward L. (Dr.) (Box A-77, Folder 164)
    - Mais, Fannie Wooden (Mrs.) (Box A-77, Folder 165)
    - Mais, Joseph (Box A-77, Folder 166)
      Photographer if identified: Jerry Darvin
    - Mais, Wilfred (Mrs.) (Box A-77, Folder 167)
    - Maitama-Sule, Yuseff (Box A-77, Folder 168)
    - Maize, Valerie (Box A-77, Folder 169)
    - Maize, William (Mr. & Mrs.) (Box A-77, Folder 170)
    - Majekodunmi, Edward Olabode (Box A-77, Folder 171)
    - Majester, Red (Box A-77, Folder 172)
    - Majete, Clayton (Box A-77, Folder 173)
      Photographer if identified: Dave Greene Photo
    - Majette, Douglas (Mr. & Mrs.) (Box A-77, Folder 174)
    - Majette, Vallie (Mr.) (Box A-77, Folder 175)
    - Major, Flo (Box A-77, Folder 176)
    - Majors, The (Group) (Box A-77, Folder 177)
    - Major, Harold (Box A-77, Folder 178)
    - Major, Geraldyn Dismond (Box A-77, Folder 179)
      Also 14 negatives (25 images total).
      Photographer if identified: W. Smith, Dummett, Office National Du Tourisme,
    - Major, Gerri (Box A-77, Folder 180)
      Also one velox print stuck to back of a print.
      Photographer if identified: Sylvia Hairston
    - Major, Jacqueline (Box A-77, Folder 181)
    - Major, James J. (Box A-77, Folder 182)
    - Major, Julian (Box A-77, Folder 183)
    - Major, L. (Box A-77, Folder 184)
    - Major, Louis (Box A-77, Folder 185)
    - Major, Russell C. (Box A-77, Folder 186)
    - Major, Tony (Box A-77, Folder 187)
      One print has single typescript leaf on verso.
    - Majors, Robert E. (Mr.) (Box A-77, Folder 188)
    - Makatini, Johisionie (Box A-77, Folder 189)
      Number of Prints:
    - Makeba, Miriam (Box A-77, Folder 190)
      Also one velox print. One print has typescript press release (three leaves) attached with paperclip
      Photographer if identified: Wagner International Photos Inc., Ronnie Brathwaite, M. Jaffe, Burley Photo Syndicate
    - Makeba, Miriam (Box A-77, Folder 191)
      Also one velox print. Two prints have single-leaf press releases attached with paperclip; one has typescript leaf press release (three leaves) attached with paperclip.
      Photographer if identified: Pictorial Enterprise, Raymond Ross, Uwe Steinberg, Kwame Brathwaite
    - Makel, Eleanor (Dr.) (Box A-77, Folder 192)
    - Makel, Joseph F. (Box A-77, Folder 193)
      Photographer if identified: Dummett, Davis, Tommy Weber
    - Makell, Tali (Box A-77, Folder 194)
      One print has single-leaf press release attached on verso.
    - Makennan, Ato Tasson (Box A-77, Folder 195)
    - Makhane, Catherine (Box A-77, Folder 196)
    - "Making Pearl" (Box A-77, Folder 197)
    - Makonnen, L. E. (Box A-77, Folder 198)
    - Makonnen, Prince (Box A-77, Folder 199)
      Note on folder: "Deceased."
      Photographer if identified: Blackstone Studios
    - Makonner, Herfe (Box A-77, Folder 200)
    - Makowicz, Adam (Box A-77, Folder 201)
    - Maksoud, Clovis (Box A-77, Folder 202)
    - Malabet, Raul (Box A-77, Folder 203)
    - Malacht, John (Box A-77, Folder 204)
    - Malafronte, Ann (Box A-77, Folder 205)
    - Malaret, Maria (Box A-77, Folder 206)
      Print is cut out and mounted on paper. Also one velox print.
    - Malave, Martin Dilan (Box A-77, Folder 207)
    - Malcioln, Jose (Box A-77, Folder 208)
    - Malcioln, Jose V. (Box A-77, Folder 209)
    - Malcolm, Benjamin (Box A-77, Folder 210)
      Two prints have single-leaf press releases attached.
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, Isaac Berez
    - Malcolm, Erna (Box A-77, Folder 211)
    - Malcolm, Kim (Box A-77, Folder 212)
      Photographer if identified: John P. Batok
    - Malcolm-King Harlem College (Box A-77, Folder 213)
      Also one computer-printed typescript leaflet (four leaves) and one computer-printed typescript packet (nine leaves) entitled "Announcing The Center For Biomedical Education" paperclipped together in folder.
    - Malcolm, Walter (Box A-77, Folder 214)
    - Maldonado, Yudelka (Box A-77, Folder 215)
    - Malecela, John W. S. (Box A-77, Folder 216)
      Photographer if identified: Art Williams
    - Maleska, Eugene T. (Dr.) (Box A-77, Folder 217)
      Print has single typescript leaf attached with staple on border.
    - Malik-Ahmed Abdul (Box A-77, Folder 218)
      Photographer if identified: Charles V. Passela
    - Maliwa, Emily (Dr.) (Box A-77, Folder 219)
      Photographer if identified: Kingsley W. Grant
    - Malla, Jah (Box A-77, Folder 220)
    - Mallard, Amy (Box A-77, Folder 221)
      One print has single typescript leaf description attached with paperclip.
      Photographer if identified: Hicks Photo Studio, Nichols, Frank's Photo
    - Mallard, Hubert (Box A-77, Folder 222)
    - Mallard, Susan (Box A-77, Folder 223)
      Print has typescript press release (two leaves) attached with paperclip.
      Photographer if identified: Ted Neuhoff
    - Mallard, William (Detective) (Box A-77, Folder 224)
    - Mallea, Juan (Box A-77, Folder 225)
    - Mallett, E. Mitchell (Rev.) (Box A-77, Folder 226)
    - Mallette, Florence (Box A-77, Folder 227)
    - Malliet, Sylvanie C. (Box A-77, Folder 228)
    - Mallomar (Group) (Box A-77, Folder 229)
    - Mallory, Arenia C. (Dr.) (Box A-77, Folder 230)
      Also one paper stereotype matrix and one negative (one image total). One print has single typescript leaf attached with paperclip.
      Photographer if identified: Nichols, Photokraft, Fred Harris, Beadle's Studio
    - Mallory, Carrie (Box A-77, Folder 231)
    - Mallory, Dolly (Box A-77, Folder 232)
    - Mallory, Eddie (Box A-77, Folder 233)
    - Mallory, Edward (Mr. & Mrs.) (Box A-77, Folder 234)
      Photographer if identified: W. Smith, Cecil Layne, Dummett
    - Mallory, Elsie (Box A-77, Folder 235)
    - Mallory, Jeanette (Box A-77, Folder 236)
    - Mallory, Jeanette (Box A-77, Folder 237)
    - Mallory, Jim (Box A-77, Folder 238)
    - Mallory, Mae (Box A-77, Folder 239)
    - Mallory, Mae (Box A-77, Folder 240)
      Photographer if identified: Burley
    - Mallory, Reuben (Dr. + Mrs.) (Box A-77, Folder 241)
    - Mallory, Rosalind (Box A-77, Folder 242)
      Photographer if identified: Henry Verby
    - Mallory, Tyrone (Box A-77, Folder 243)
    - Mallory, Wesley (Box A-77, Folder 244)
    - Malone, Annie M. Turnbo (Box A-77, Folder 245)
      One paper stereotype matrix with single-leaf press release attached with paperclip.
    - Malombo (Box A-77, Folder 246)
    - Malone, Afreda (Box A-77, Folder 247)
    - Malone, Ivey (Box A-77, Folder 248)
    - Malone, James (Box A-77, Folder 249)
      Photographer if identified: American Red Cross
    - Malone, John (Box A-77, Folder 250)
    - Malone, Rhonda (Box A-77, Folder 251)
    - Malone, Robert (Box A-77, Folder 252)
      One paper stereotype matrix with single-leaf press release attached with staple on border.
    - Malone, Stanley R. (Attorney) (Box A-77, Folder 253)
    - Malone, Thomas (Dr.) (Box A-77, Folder 254)
    - Malone, Vivian (Box A-77, Folder 255)
    - Malone, Walter (Box A-77, Folder 256)
    - Maloney, A. H. (Dr.) (Box A-77, Folder 257)
      Photographer if identified: Morgan & Marvin Smith
    - Maloney, Charles (Box A-77, Folder 258)
    - Maloney, Clyde (Box A-77, Folder 259)
      Photographer if identified: Layne's Studio, Lane Photographers
    - Maloney, Elaine (Box A-77, Folder 260)
    - Maloney, Julie (Box A-77, Folder 261)
      Photographer if identified: Tom Caravaglia
    - Maloney, MacDonald (Box A-77, Folder 262)
      Also one negative (one image total).
    - Maloney, Stephen N. (Box A-77, Folder 263)
    - Maloy, Johnnie (Mrs.) (Box A-77, Folder 264)
    - Malsin, Raphael (Box A-77, Folder 265)
    - Malveaux, Antoinette (Box A-77, Folder 266)
      Print has staple through image.
    - Malveaux, Maora (Box A-77, Folder 267)
    - Malveaux, Vincent (Box A-77, Folder 268)
    - Malverne, L. I. (Box A-77, Folder 269)
    - "Mama I Want To Sing" (Box A-77, Folder 270)
      Note on folder: "Theatre."
    - Mamby, Saoul (Box A-77, Folder 271)
      Photographer if identified: Glenn Edwards
    - A Man Called Adam (Box A-78, Folder 1)
      Also script synopsis of movie.
    - Man Called Adam (Box A-78, Folder 2)
      4 prints are mounted on newsprint with adhesive.
    - Manago, Rickie (Box A-78, Folder 3)
    - Manana, Matiwane (Box A-78, Folder 4)
    - Manasse, Ernst M. (Dr.) (Box A-78, Folder 5)
      Print has caption stapled to recto.
    - Manbrook Combo (Box A-78, Folder 6)
    - Junior Mance (Box A-78, Folder 7)
    - Mance, Robert W. (Box A-78, Folder 8)
    - Manchester, Melissa (Box A-78, Folder 9)
    - Mancini, Ray Boom Boom (Box A-78, Folder 10)
    - Mandal, Ashis Kumar (Dr.) (Box A-78, Folder 11)
    - Father, Abba Laike-Marian Mandefio (See Imahoy Kristos Semia) (Box A-78, Folder 12)
    - Mandelman, Ruth (Box A-78, Folder 13)
    - Mandeville, Edgar O. (Dr.) (Box A-78, Folder 14)
      Photographer if identified: Bob Head, Pictorial Enterprise
    - Mandez, Olga (Box A-78, Folder 15)
    - Mandingo (Box A-78, Folder 16)
    - Mandrill (Box A-78, Folder 17)
      Also folder with album slicks, show flier. Multi-page biography. 2 prints are stuck together with paste.
    - Manes, Donald (Box A-78, Folder 18)
      Also 2 velox prints. Facsimile of proclamation.
      Photographer if identified: Frank Parlatore,
    - Manes, Donald (Box A-78, Folder 19)
      Photographer if identified: Bill Hayes,
    - Maney, C. D. (Dr.) See D. J. T. Hodxie (Box A-78, Folder 20)
    - Manfort, Paul J. (Box A-78, Folder 21)
    - Mangano, Silvana (Box A-78, Folder 22)
    - Mangar, Judy Margaret (Box A-78, Folder 23)
      Photographer if identified: New York Times Studio
    - Manggrum, Douglas (Mr. & Mrs.) See Harold Bradford (Box A-78, Folder 24)
    - Mangham, Michael J. (Box A-78, Folder 25)
    - Mangiante, Vincent A. (Box A-78, Folder 26)
    - Mangione, Chuck (Box A-78, Folder 27)
    - Mango, Leroy Mr. & Mrs. (Box A-78, Folder 28)
    - Mangrum, Donna (Box A-78, Folder 29)
    - Mangual, Levs (Box A-78, Folder 30)
    - Mangum, Claude J. (Box A-78, Folder 31)
      Photographer if identified: C. B. Jones
    - Gladys Mangum (Box A-78, Folder 32)
    - Mangum, Gladys See Helen Butler (Box A-78, Folder 33)
    - Mangum, James & Dorothy (Box A-78, Folder 34)
    - Mangum, Louise (Box A-78, Folder 35)
      Photographer if identified: John P. Balok
    - Mangum, Marilyn (Box A-78, Folder 36)
    - Mangum, Richard (Box A-78, Folder 37)
    - Mangrum, Richard C. Lt. Gen. (See Archie Moore) (Box A-78, Folder 38)
    - Mangum, Robert J. (Box A-78, Folder 39)
      Also newspaper clipping, 3 velox prints. 1 print has newspaper clipping taped to verso. 2 prints are stuck together.
      Photographer if identified: A. Hansen, Ralph Cooper, Cecil Layne, David McAdams, Gilbert Pictorial Enterprise, Studio of the New York Times, E. McDonald, Standard Studios,
    - Mangum, Robert J. (Box A-78, Folder 40)
      Also one press release and a typescript note from RJM.
      Photographer if identified: Studio of the New York Times, Nichols, Cecil Layne, Hamilton Associates,
    - Manhattan Borough Community Planning District #10 (Box A-78, Folder 41)
    - Manhattan Central Medical Society (Box A-78, Folder 42)
      Also 4 envelopes of negatives (details below.) 2 prints have staples through edge.
      Photographer if identified: Nichols, L. St. Clair Dummett, W. Smith, A. Adams, Layne's Studio, James C. Campbell, Photokraft,
    - 1 - Man. Central Medical Boat Ride [Dummett] (Box A-78, Folder 42)
      Dated 7-6-1951. 2 strips of 6"x6" negatives. 4 images.
    - 2 - Women's Aux - Manhattan Med. Society Skyline [Nichols] (Box A-78, Folder 42)
      Dated 5-19-1951. 1 strip of 6"x6" negatives. 3 images.
    - 3 - Manhattan Medical 2E 103 [word crossed out] Testimonial Dinner Dr. Caul [Dummett] (Box A-78, Folder 42)
      Dated 2-7-1951. 1 strip of 6"x6" negatives. 2 images.
    - 4 - Med Aux 284 Convent Ave Installation of Officers [Dummett] (Box A-78, Folder 42)
      Dated 6-24-1950. 1 strip of 6"x6" negatives. 2 images.
    - Manhattan Community Center (Box A-78, Folder 43)
    - Manhattan Community College (Box A-78, Folder 44)
      Ms. captions loose in folder.
      Photographer if identified: Laima Turnley, Louis Checkman, Camera Associates, Jay Sharp, Bro. David McAdams,
    - Manhattan Debonaires S. C. (Box A-78, Folder 45)
    - Manhattan Gauchos (Box A-78, Folder 46)
    - Manhattan Neighborhood Improvement Assn. (Box A-78, Folder 47)
      Photographer if identified: Te-Dal Studios
    - Manhattan Paul (Box A-78, Folder 48)
      Also one paper stereotype matrix, envelope of negatives. One print has staple through edge.
      Photographer if identified: Herbert Hawkins, James Campbell, Nichols,
    - 1 - Manhattan Paul & Group Sailing SS Franconia Pier 92 [Nichols] (Box A-78, Folder 48)
      Dated 1-18-1952. 1 strip and 1 loose frame, 6"x6" negatives. 3 images.
    - Manhattan Riot (Mid) 1967 (Box A-78, Folder 49)
    - Manhattan School of Music (Box A-78, Folder 50)
      Also program for 1966 season opener.
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, Whitestone Photo
    - Manhattan Sharks (Box A-78, Folder 51)
    - Manhattans Singing Group [The Manhattans] (Box A-78, Folder 52)
      2 prints have staples through edge.
      Photographer if identified: Allan Luftig, Peterkin Photo, James J. Kriegsmann, Pictorial Enterprise,
    - Manhattan Valley Day Care Center (Box A-78, Folder 53)
    - Manhattanaires Drum & Bugle Corps. (Box A-78, Folder 54)
    - The Manhattans (Box A-78, Folder 55)
    - Manhattan Transfer (Box A-78, Folder 56)
    - Manhole (Box A-78, Folder 57)
    - Manhood Foundations (Box A-78, Folder 58)
    - Maniac (Box A-78, Folder 59)
    - Manicurists (Box A-78, Folder 60)
    - Manigault, Earl (Box A-78, Folder 61)
    - Manigault, William (Box A-78, Folder 62)
      Photographer if identified: Carol
    - Manigaulte, John W. Dr. (Box A-78, Folder 63)
    - Manino, Joe (Box A-78, Folder 64)
      Print mounted on cardboard and stuck to folder.
    - Mankins, Pearl (Box A-78, Folder 65)
    - Abe Manley (Box A-78, Folder 66)
    - Manley, Albert E. (Dr.) (Box A-78, Folder 67)
    - Manley, Effa (Mrs.) (Box A-78, Folder 68)
      Photographer if identified: James H. Purdy,
    - Manley, Hazel (Box A-78, Folder 69)
    - Manley, Helen & Joel (Box A-78, Folder 70)
    - Manley, Ivory (Box A-78, Folder 71)
    - Manley, James J. (Ptl.) (Box A-78, Folder 72)
    - Manley, Joel Dr. & Mrs. (Box A-78, Folder 73)
    - Manley, John D. (Box A-78, Folder 74)
    - Manley, John B. (Dr.) (Box A-78, Folder 75)
    - Manley, Milo (Box A-78, Folder 76)
      Also 1 envelope of negatives.
      Photographer if identified: L. St. Clair Dummett, G. Marshall Wilson, Nichols
    - 1 - Milo Manley office [Nichols] (Box A-78, Folder 76)
      Dated 6-11-1947. 2 4"x5" negatives. 2 images.
    - Manley, Michael (Box A-78, Folder 77)
      Also 1 illustration, 4 velox prints. 2 prints have staples through edge.
      Photographer if identified: Bill Moore, Agency For Public Information/Harvey, Ted Cunningham, 667 Group, Curt Clemons, Jamaica Information Service, United Nations/M. Tzovaras,
    - Manley, Norman (Box A-78, Folder 78)
      Photographer if identified: L. St. Clair Dummett,
    - Manley, Patty (Box A-78, Folder 79)
    - Manly, Douglas (Box A-78, Folder 80)
    - Mann, Alicia (Box A-78, Folder 81)
      Photographer if identified: Mr. A. Benners
    - Mann, Barbara (Box A-78, Folder 82)
    - Mann, Bernie (Box A-78, Folder 83)
    - Mann, Bobby (Box A-78, Folder 84)
    - Mann, Dolores (Box A-78, Folder 85)
    - Hattie Mann (Box A-78, Folder 86)
    - Mann, Herbie (Box A-78, Folder 87)
    - Mann, Howard R. (Box A-78, Folder 88)
    - 1 - Howard Mann organist [Nichols] (Box A-78, Folder 88)
      Dated 7-26-1949. 1 loose 6"x6" frame. 1 image.
    - Mann, Howard Sr. (Box A-78, Folder 89)
      Photographer if identified: Lee Luckett
    - Mann, John Wesley (Box A-78, Folder 90)
    - Mann, Joseph B. Jr. (Box A-78, Folder 91)
      2 prints are stuck together with paste. One print has staple through edge.
      Photographer if identified: Bill Mackey, Gilbert Pictorial Enterprise, Wagner International
    - Lt. Marion Mann (Box A-78, Folder 92)
    - Mann, Millicent (Box A-78, Folder 93)
      Photographer if identified: C. Ramsey